subs by maro!
I was very surprised when I first heard
it, but I'm looking forward to it.
I want to be a person who can deliver
dreams and hopes.
This program is a program where six
people who are determined to promote
something exciting
and complete their dreams while doing
their best!
Thank you for watching!
I'm nervous, but I'm looking forward to
seeing how they react.
Are you already there?
I'm going to close the door.
Thank you for watching. Please
subscribe to our channel.
I will introduce the new member.
Are you okay? Please come.
Come here.
What?
Aki-chan.
Wow.
I'm Tada Aki.
I'll do my best.
Nice to meet you.
I see.
Aki-chan.
I'm Tada Aki.
I'm Suda Aki, a 15-year-old high school
freshman.
When I first heard the name, I was very
surprised, but I'm looking forward to
it.
I was nervous while taking dance
lessons and voice lessons.
This song gave me the element of being
you, Inori Miokin.
I liked this song the most.
[♪ Solomon ♪
For real!?
Her courtesan image
All of them are twinkling
As a group
I thought that they bonded
It's dazzling
In the song
For example, in the chorus,
when we sing the chorus together,
if one person is off key, it's weird.
It's like, huh? Someone's off key.
So we don't break the cycle.
We're trying to sing like the members
of TokiSEN.
It's a very positive song.
And the lyrics are not just a part of
the song.
Every lyrics are very relatable.
Not only a part of the song, but
everyone will agree with the lyrics.
I can really relate to the lyrics.
It's very bright.
When I first heard it, I thought it was
cool and I thought it would be fun to
perform it live.
I wanted to dance to it as soon as
possible.
It's a very energetic, positive, and
positive song.
I thought it was a cheerful song that
made me feel better.
The lyrics are very positive.
I felt like I was running forward from
the beginning.
I felt like I was moving.
I felt like everything was fine.
I can't wait to perform it live.
It's a very fun song.
It's the song I've never been able to
get back to before.
I'm a little nervous.
I'm so happy.
I'm having fun.
I'll do my best. Thank you.
Thank you. Bye-bye.
Bye-bye.
I'll do my best.
I'm so embarrassed.
Thank you.
The song is a bright and fun song.
I have.
But I like the sound.
I want to sing Princess Princess
Princess or Gamba or Gamushara.
I want to sing more perfectly.
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you very much.
It was fun.
I was nervous.
I was surprised at first because I
could hear my voice loudly.
I was nervous.
I was not good at some parts, but it
was hard.
I want you to do it again.
I'm going to enter the stage later.
I'm worried that I might break the
formation.
I don't want to lose the stability I
have now.
I want to dance properly.
I was a little worried about that.
I'm nervous.
What is this?
It's a great move.
I want to be a desirable person.
I want to be a person who can deliver
dreams and hopes.
that.
We will support you with all our might.
Let's do our best together.
Thank you.
Aki is the new member.
We are the closest to each other.
Let's get along well.
Julia is older than me.
I will learn a lot from this tour.
I will be in pain.
I will be worried about my future.
We will support you with all our might.
I will be the 6th member.
I want to keep going.
I almost cried.
I want to make my dream come true with
these 6 members.
We will be back to the beginning and do
our best with the same feeling.
Thank you.
I'm the last one.
You're cute.
I think Aki-chan's brightness will make
a new number of people.
I think the fans will follow us with
Aki-chan's brightness.
Let's be confident and do our best to
make our dreams come true in this
country.
Thank you.
I was surprised.
Let's do our best.
I think I'll be very desperate to
follow you at first.
I want to overcome it and go to various
worlds with everyone.
New clothes
Isn't it cute?
I want to go to various worlds with
everyone.
That's all for today!
Hi! Hi! Long time no see!